A nine -year -old girl in New Mexico has raised more than $500 for her little
brother who needs heart surgery in Houston, Texas, this July.
Addison Witulski's grandmother, Kim Allred, said Addison probably overheard a
conversation between family members.
Addison Witulski's grandmother, Kim Allred,
Addison probably overheard a conversation between family members.
Addison Witulski's grandmother, Kim Allred, said Addison probably overheard a
conversation between family members.
Talking about the funds needed to get her little brother to treatment.
I guess she overheard her grandfather and me talking about how we are worried.
About how we are going to get to Houston for my grandson's heart surgery, said
Allred. how we are going to get to Houston for my grandson's heart surgery, said
Allred. About how we are going to get to Houston for my grandson's heart surgery,
said Allred. She decided to go outside and have a lemonade stand and make some
drawings and pictures and sell them.
decided to go outside and have a lemonade stand and make some drawings and pictures
and sell them.
She decided to go outside and have a lemonade stand and make some drawings and
pictures and sell them.
That's when Addison and her friends, Erica and Emily Borden, decided to sell
lemonade for 50 cents a cup and sell pictures for 25 cents each.
lemonade for 50 cents a cup and sell pictures for